Visit our website for more: turkision.com
No living being was harmed during the
filming of this series.
Episode 111
Let's go!
I had to go too.
What if something happened
to my father?
I can't wait like this.
I will go.
Calm down, Bala.
Inshallah, nothing will
happen to our Sheikh.
Alps and the Sisters are in Yenişehir.
Do not worry.
No bird will fly without our knowledge.
Keep your eyes open, Ayşe.
Ülgen Hatun sent me.
She sent me saying you didn't
eat anything, so at least drink this.
Thank you.
It is important.
I'll see Halime.
Bala.
Do not worry.
Brothers! Come on!
Come on!
Boran, shields won't hold.
It's a trap.
It's a trap, brothers, move!
We'll take shelter in shields.
Come on!
Let's go!
Open.
Take cover!
My Bey will enter the Khanqah, brothers.
We will enter the Khan.
Let's go!
It's a trap, take cover.
My Bey, what are we going to do?
Wait, Alps!
Wait.
Now!
Take cover!
Open.
Take cover.
Alps!
Be careful.
There is no sound.
Let's go slowly.
Let's go.
What's going on, Esma? Why did you
summon me?
They asked me to give you this.
However, they
commanded that only you should see it.
Who gave you this?
Someone I do not know.
However, Mother Sultan has sent it...
...just for you.
Sheikh Edebali is at Marmaracık Castle.
You'll be there alone by noon.
If you try to deceive me in any way...
Or if you don't come, your
father will die, Bala Hatun.
You or your father.
İsmihan.
Who is it, Esma?
I ask you who is she? I don't know.
I swear, I don't know!
I don't know!
Esma, it's up to my father!
If you are lying...
I will not forgive you.
A man came...
and put a paper in my hand.
He said it is from
Mother Sultan.
He told me to give it to Bala Hatun only.
I don't know anything else.
My Sheikh, my Sheikh!
My Sheikh.
Who did this to my Sheikh?
I will drown him in his blood.
Tell Sultan quickly.
Sultan Mesut.
Osman Bey.
Where is the Sheikh?
They're going inside now.
Hurry up, come
on, Mesut, come on!
Let's go!
Nobody knows this secret place.
Come on, inside, come on.
I will not leave you, Sheikh
Edebali.
No, never mind, Mesut.
They don't know you exist.
They are coming to get me.
Hide now to spoil their
games when the time is right, come on.
Come on.
Come on, take it
and it'll stay with you.
Faster.
Let's go.
Arrested the Sheikh.
Yazid.
Yazid!
İsmihan raided the Khanqah and took him.
Sheikh Edebali
sacrificed himself for me.
What?
I will shed the blood of those
who did this to my Sheikh.
No.
My Bey!
Greek fire!
My Sultan!
My Sheikh.
Don't you dare!
Don't do anything without knowing.
Malhun.
Where are you late?
She went saying she was going to check
on Halima and she hasn't come back yet.
Shall we go see her?
Or did she go to Söğüt?
Malhun Hatun.
I will tell you something.
Esma, where is Bala?
Bala Hatun.
She sent you news.
What news?
She told you to
go to Osman Bey as soon as possible.
She said they lured Osman Bey into a trap.
What are you saying, Esma?
Bala Hatun.
She went to surrender to Mother Sultan.
Are you okay, Sultan Mesut?
Cerkutay.
- My Bey.
- Cerkutay.
Come.
Look at the entrance of the
road.
How is it? Let's go!
Gürbüz, take Sultan there, come on.
They are coming in
great numbers, my Bey.
Take it, take it, take it!
Put it.
They are waiting for us, it will be
difficult for us to get out of here.
So that's what you say.
So let them come.
Let them come.
We were looking for Mesut.
Now, you will both die.
We do not have a soul to
give to dogs and foxes!
We'll chop off your heads first, and then
the heads of those above you.
Come.
İsmihan Sultan.
You make people kill each other.
You will pay very badly for this.
Sultan Mesut.
Are you well?
I see you are very surprised.
Or did our arrival disturb you?
I ask forgiveness from
Allah, Mother Sultan.
The castle is yours.
I am here because I trust you.
We are pleased with your
confidence, Mother Sultan.
But, my Sheikh...
Why is he restricted?
What is happening?
Sheikh Edebali is under arrest.
From now on, no one will speak to
him without my permission.
Avcı Bey.
Take Sheikh Edebali to
the dungeon.
What is the crime committed by Sheikh
Edebali to throw him in prison?
Also, does Osman Bey
know about this?
Sorry, Mother Sultan.
Forgive her.
Excuse her for what she said
because of her young age.
I'll ignore this for your
sake, Bengi Hatun.
Avcı Bey.
Deploy the soldiers in the castle.
Do not leave any place empty.
And raise our flags!
From now on, no one will leave the
castle without my permission.
Increase your precautions, Öktem Bey.
Osman will do something.
What's the situation, Boran?
İsmihan was not there
when we came, Malhun Hatun.
She left those here.
Where is Osman?
In the Khanqah.
Well, what about Konur?
Baysungur and the Alps
went to the dungeon to see him.
Be careful.
Go to dungeon, Kumral Abdal.
And I'll go to the Khanqah.
Come on, Alps.
Konur, my brother.
My Allah.
Konur.
Dear Konur, what have they
done to you, my brave brother?
Everyone, stay away!
Go away, go away!
Baysungur.
Did you touch him?
What do you say, Kumral Abdal?
These wounds...
he is burning.
This is not good at all.
Don't get close to him.
Konur is breathing...
but he is weak.
It may be an infectious disease.
Tell the rest of the doctors
immediately, Şamil.
Come on, let's all get out, come on.
My Bey, İsmihan is in Marmaracık.
Our Sheikh is with her, too.
How do you know, Malhun?
İsmihan sent a message to Bala.
She told her that her father is a prisoner of
hers, if she doesn't come, know that he'll be killed.
She told her to come to
Marmaracık without telling anyone.
Don't say that, Malhun.
Malhun.
Don't say that Bala is gone.
Do not say that.
She's gone, my Bey.
Malhun.
We found out later, so
I couldn't stop her.
You've gone too far, İsmihan.
İsmihan.
Both my Sheikh and Bala.
You took them from me.
You are...
No, I will take them both back.
I will not leave them to you!
I will not leave them.
I will get them both back!
Sultan Mesut.
They want you.
They want you, my Sultan.
I told you, Osman Bey.
I am a mess.
My wreck befalls
those who stand beside me.
Even if you describe yourself
as a mess...
I need you.
I know İsmihan.
And I know you too.
And you will know me too, this
will be over.
I will not give her either
my loved ones...
or you.
So what are we going to do, Osman Bey?
I will hide you in a place
where no one will know.
Aykut will know
where you're going.
Your command, my Bey. I will take Sultan
to the safest place, Inshallah.
Come on, my Sultan.
My Bey!
Konur is in
the dungeon.
However, he is ill...
...and his disease is contagious.
İsmihan clearly did this on purpose.
And not just Konur.
This disease is seen
in Söğüt too.
The people are sick.
The situation is dangerous.
So that's why they left Söğüt...
and made Marmaracık their headquarters.
Tell me.
Konur...
Can we save him?
We will do our best, my Bey.
We will continue to pray for him.
So...
We will make Söğüt
our impenetrable fortress.
- Malhun.
- Yes, my Bey.
Together with the Alps, you
will control Söğüt.
Kumral Abdal, this disease won't spread
from here, you'll solve this problem.
Malhun, do your best and keep the
disease away from Söğüt.
Don't worry, my Bey.
I'm going to take my
Sheikh and Bala.
- Mal Allah save you.
- Thank you.
Come on, Alps!
Come on, come on.
Sheikh Edebali.
is in our dungeon.
What are these days we live in, my Allah?
What could we have done, we
couldn't say no to Mother Sultan.
We had to.
They won't stop.
As long as Osman cannot stop
and no one stops him...
...he will cause misfortune
to many people.
Allah exists, Bengi.
Sheikh Edebali is one of Allah's saints.
Do you think they will be
successful, those who did this to him?
We're on the wrong path.
Let Osman hear about this...
and the castle will be
demolished over our heads.
He can't destroy it, Öktem Bey.
He can't destroy it.
Mother Sultan.
The castle is under my rule.
Who is Osman Bey to attack
the places I rule?
My Sultan.
Sheikh Edebali is not only
important to Osman Bey.
He is important for all Turks.
He is Allah's saint.
I'm afraid...
Nothing to fear.
Öktem Bey.
I know what you know.
May you also know what I know.
Osman hides Mesut.
If he gives me Mesut...
I will give him Sheikh Edebali.
Is our state a state of infidels that we
can be hostile to Allah's saint?
Now, tell me.
Will you stand by Osman Bey, who rebelled
against the Seljuk state?
Or will you stand by me?
Of course, I will stand by you.
And now...
I will increase the measures
if you allow me.
I trust you absolutely.
Bengi Hatun.
Thanks to you, we will have another guest.
I have sent news to Bala Hatun.
She will come here to save her father.
She insulted me.
She deceived me.
Did you think I'd let her
go unpunished?
Never.
I forgive everything..
but I do not forgive this.
I'll make her regret, Bengi Hatun.
I will punish her so hard that...
everyone will be afraid to cross their
boundaries with me again.
And what about Sheikh
Edebali, Mother Sultan?
Are you going to let him go?
Halime, my beautiful daughter.
No.
You will be
angry with your mother.
I know you will be upset, but
don't be upset or angry
I'll go now but I...
I won't worry.
Mother.
What is happening?
Is there bad news?
- My sheikh?
- No, son, no.
Come on, come, sit down.
Your father summoned me to Söğüt.
You will take care of your sister, right?
She is so young.
Take good care of her.
Take care of her until l I come back.
I entrust you to Alla and
entrust you to each other.
Don't worry, mother.
Halime.
Let's go.
Forgive me, Osman.
Forgive me.
Tell Osman and my children..
that Bala loves them more than her soul.
Come on, go, girl.
Let's go.
Let us go from this direction, Sultan.
Let us go and see, Aykut Alp, how
far we can go?
Yenişehir/Osman Bey's Palace
I shouldn't have left my
mother alone, I'm late.
Aladdin.
- Where are you going?
- I'll go to my mother.
I will not go back without
taking my mother.
This is not possible, my brother.
We cannot move without
an order from my Bey.
Halime will search for you, will you leave
her alone in the absence of your mother?
What's your use then, Ülgen Hatun?
What if something happened to my mother,
what would I tell my sister then?
When she grows up, won't she tell me why
did I leave my mother alone?
What will I say when she tells me "Why
didn't you prevent her from going?"
Tell me, what will I say?
Am I going to tell her I just sat
doing nothing, what am I going to say?
Aladdin.
Look, brother.
We now have the biggest duties.
Especially your duty.
We will not move without an
order from Osman Bey.
He must guide us to the right path.
İsmihan Sultan.
Come out.
Bala Hatun.
You came.
You seem to be in a hurry.
I have come and here I am before you.
Leave my father now.
Leave your father?
His time will come, Bala Hatun, be
patient a little.
Your problem is with me, and here I am.
Leave my father, then.
Yes, my problem is with you.
You've crossed the line with what you've done.
You deserved a lesson.
Soldiers, arrest her!
Let me go! Will you give
me a lesson, İsmihan?
You are a coward.
You're so helpless that you couldn't
come out to me on your own.
- You...
- You confuse courage with stupidity.
You are not brave.
You've surrendered.
Is this courage?
You don't seem to know anything
about courage, love and fidelity.
- You'll die without knowing this, İsmihan.
- You impudent one.
Bala Hatun.
Alçiçek.
You played a game on me.
You put your hand on what belongs to me.
Did you think this would go
unpunished?
You thought you could sow the seeds
of discord between us, but you were wrong.
However, your evil games didn't
separate us, and now you...
Bala.
İsmihan! Now, go outside!
Osman.
Bala.
İsmihan! Go outside if you have
the courage to do so.
Take her to the dungeon.
Osman, let me go!
Osman!
Bala.
Osman! Leave me alone!
Get out!
Leave me!
Where?
Bala.
İsmihan! Go outside!
Get out!
Osman! This is the truth
you do not understand.
You are at the bottom and I am at the top.
You are defeated and I am victorious.
I swear I'll blow this
place over your head.
I'll burn this summit on which
you are sitting to the ground.
You won't be able to do anything while
your Sheikh and wife are my captives.
Don't waste your breath.
Even if it's my last breath, I'll take
them from your hands.
This is easy.
If you bring Mesut to me, I
will set them free.
It's like that.
I won't give you those who took refuge in
me and I won't leave my loved ones with you.
Wake up, Osman!
This is power.
You no longer have any
judgment over the border areas.
Resistance will only bring blood.
As for
surrendering, it requires sacrifice.
We give our heads and souls, but
we never give up!
You and those behind you should know
that I'll make this place a grave for you.
If you bring one catapult
to these walls...
you'll be the one who beheads
your Sheikh and your wife.
You have time
until tomorrow evening Osman.
If Mesut doesn't
come by tomorrow evening...
dig two graves for your
Sheikh and for your wife.
Only what Allah wants will happen.
Let's go.
Send the men to the nearby places...
to collect all the supplies
that are there.
Tonight, we will prepare a wonderful dinner.
My lover.
Olof.
What did you do?
I have decided to fight for
the religion of Jesus.
How do you betray Odin?
Odin will curse us.
The black curse will always
follow us!
No, Frigg, it's over.
The religion of Jesus
has given me an army!
What did Odin give me?
Olof! The souls of the warriors in
Valhalla are with us.
Odin has sent them to take revenge.
As Odin turned his back on
me, Jesus' religion embraced me.
Besides, I have not seen any
soul kill an enemy for us.
Let me!
Are these the warriors?
Which one would
sacrifice his life for you?
Do not underestimate the army of Jesus.
We shall take the lands, upon which
we shall live, with these men.
Everything is prepared for us.
It's all set for us, Frigg.
For us?
Kantakuzenos' dog!
That is enough.
That's enough, Frigg.
That's enough.
Olof.
What are we doing?
What are we doing
here?
Territory and revenge.
I am the one who will
grant you this revenge.
I didn't love you for Odin's sake.
İsmihan wants you by her
side in Marmaracık.
She will take everything
he owns from Osman.
Even his soul.
How good news!
"Allah Almighty speaks the truth."
Don't cry, sister.
Mother will come.
She will come.
My heart is being torn.
Don't cry.
My Allah.
You care for the helpless...
and heal them.
Bring us together with my mother and
grandfather, my Allah.
Help us, my Allah.
You are the ruler.
You are the Malik.
For my sister who is
crying in her cradle...
and for the sanctity of our Prophet, the
Messenger of Allah...
do not test us by losing
our mother, my Allah.
Open.
Don't touch me!
Bala!
I'll go myself, don't touch me!
Remove your hand!
My dear.
My father!
- Bala.
- Father!
Leave me!
Don't touch my daughter!
- My father.
- My dear.
Leave her.
Leave my daughter!
Leave her!
Father.
My dear.
What did they do
to you like that?
My Father!
I have come, my
Sheikh, I am here.
Don't touch me!
My father.
What are you doing here?
Dear Bala.
She said she's going to kill you, father.
What could I do?
Martyrdom is a meeting
point for us, my daughter.
If it exists in our destiny, we have it.
Otherwise..
We will miss our Allah for a long time.
My Father.
İsmihan handcuffed us.
She plunged her dagger into
our warm body...
moved it slowly.
What do you think a
wounded wolf might do?
Pounce and attack, my Bey.
Exactly.
We will never stop
My Bey.
She said if I saw a specter of artillery
before the walls, I would kill them both.
Even though we don't have cannons...
We will get through this, Inshallah.
But it is difficult, my Bey.
If we can't get over it...
Then, we will find another solution.
But we will not give up.
We will never think of giving up.
Tell us hit so we hit!
Tell us die and
we will die, my Bey!
What are we going to do?
We will rapidly increase
the number of Alps.
Bring shovels.
We'll start digging a tunnel.
We will enter the corridors
inside the wall.
We will keep digging as much as we can.
Before sunrise...
We will end this, Inshallah.
We will attack them at the
moment they least expect...
and from a place they would never expect.
But don't forget.
This is not a fight.
It is a rescue campaign.
After we entered...
we will go to the dungeon.
We will take Bala Hatun and
Sheikh Edebali.
- Boran.
- My Bey.
You will go with the Alps who are
behind you to the gate of the house.
There will be Alps at the gate as well.
After all the prisoners are
released from the dungeon....
We will kill
everyone who's there then.
Your command, my Bey.
My Bey.
There is news from Konya.
Sultan Aladdin.
He's coming here with a huge army.
We'll finish digging tonight
We will have entered the castle
before the Sultan arrives.
We don't have much time.
We are running out of time.
Come on, Boran.
Let's see.
Hurry up.
Bengi and Öktem shouldn't see you.
Their time will come, too
But, Osman first.
Follow me.
Marta.
Bengi Hatun.
Did Mother Sultan summon you?
Yes.
Did you bring the fabrics again?
But we're a little late.
Excuse me, Bengi Hatun.
Let's not keep Mother Sultan
waiting.
It causes deep wounds.
It causes a fever.
Loss of consciousness
and slowed breathing.
As if they had mixed the poison of snakes with the poison of scorpions and the poisonous hemlock plant...
...and they injected
him.
I also have never seen anything like
this before, Kumral Abdal.
It's like a plague...
but it is not.
It's not like that.
It's a different matter.
Not something I've ever seen.
Whoever caused this is
not from these lands.
Obviously he's been
like this for days.
What a strange effect.
It's slowly taking over everywhere.
Not only him...
It infected everyone in Söğüt.
If we don't find a cure for it, woe
to us, Ayşe Hatun.
We will bury our heroes one by one.
Kumral Abdal.
May Allah protect us.
You will find a cure.
You'll find, right?
The medicine is hidden
in the poison, Ayşe Hatun.
My valiant.
Get me a hemlock and a snake, but let
it be a poisonous snake...
and a scorpion.
Come on, our time is running out.
Come on.
Your command, Kumral Abdal.
Let's go.
Osman Bey.
I heard what happened.
Alps are ready.
I will transfer those in
the tribe to İnegöl.
We are ready to hit Marmaracık.
There is no hitting.
So what do we do?
I will enter Marmaracık.
And I will take back
my wife and my Sheikh.
However, your duty will be different.
Tell me.
The Sultan has gathered a large army
and is heading towards us.
You will stop it.
How many?
We can block them on the way
with some traps.
But we'll have to hit them later.
Are you going to hit
Sultan because I asked for this?
How do we stop otherwise?
Sultan is coming to see İsmihan
in Marmaracık.
You will meet them on the way.
You will make them change
their way to Söğüt.
We will host them there.
Be careful.
Marmaracık Castle
You will be held accountable for
everything you have done, İsmihan.
The day will come when you
will be held accountable.
It is you who must be held
accountable, Bala Hatun.
You raised the dagger at me.
You poisoned me and stole my seal.
You laid your hands on my
ancestral estate, Söğüt.
Do you accuse me of stealing?
I didn't just get your
ancestors' possessions...
I got your father, too.
Osman will bring Mesut.
And then...
...it will be your end.
You are so arrogant that you think you
know the time of my life and my death.
Death is in the hands of Allah.
We live as determined by fate.
But who knows?
Your life may be shorter.
Do you know what is short, Sheikh Edebali?
Your dream of establishing a state.
That dream was born dead!
You don't know that!
Even if you have power to kill us...
That dream will live forever!
How many of us can you take down,
Ismihan?
How many of us can you kill?
One of you.
Thousand of you.
Ten thousands of you!
Whoever dreams of establishing
a state over a state!
There is no free country!
You handed over your state
to the Mongols for power!
Everyone wants power, Bala Hatun.
This is what you don't see.
And for this, I ally with enemies
if necessary!
...and I can sacrifice my people!
You can't be as brave as I am.
You can't take as much risk as I do.
Of course I can't.
There is death, Ismihan, death.
You can get what you want
in this world today...
But there's afterlife in Allah's presence.
Do not worry.
I will put you in the grave soon.
We are not afraid of death, Ismihan!
Death is not the end.
It is clear that this world has deceived you,
and has forgotten it.
Sheikh Edebali, the greatness!
You love to talk about arragonce.
You see yourselves so great...
...so great that you try playing
a game on me, on the Mother Sultan.
This is not your level.
What we have is not arrogance.
It's courage.
It should be in the heart of every Muslim.
Whether by games or weapons.
We are not afraid to object you.
Look around, sheikh Edebali.
You are in prison.
Ah.
Because you put us in jail...
...you count that as a win, right?
So listen carefully.
Prison is like a prophet's place!
Falling into the well which Joseph fell...
This is glory to us!
But Ismihan Hatun.
What you do is identical to the
Pharaoh's actions.
Wait for the time when
you will become humiliated.
When that time comes,
you will be shattered.
Whether by games or weapons.
My Bey!
- Come on.
- Oh Allah.
O Allah.
Come on, Cerkutay, we don't have much time
Hurry up a bit!
Brother.
We still have a long way to the passage
you mentioned, right Shamil?
Your knowledge of all those passages...
...will be our way out, Inshallah.
Hah?
We are getting close, my Bey.
A bit more digging and we will
see the passage, Inshallah.
We're nearly there.
We will enter the castle
and strike the infidels!
Inshallah.
Come on, Cerkutay.
Rest a little.
Come on, let's swap places.
Give me, come on.
Gurbuz!
Come Gurbuz!
Let's see, in the name of Allah!
Come on, alps, don't stay idle!
Come on!
Allah!
Gurbuz, stronger, Gurbuz!
Hang on a little more, a little more!
My sheik, my Bala!
How sure you are that you are right!
What put you there is
Osman's desire of power!
Not me.
You accuse me of being cruel!
But who pushed me to this is you.
Your rebellion! Your games!
If you want to be cruel...
...you can find many excuses.
One who was born cruel
can be cruel no matter what.
I see it in your eyes, Ismihan.
You are afraid.
You are afraid of your end both
in this world and in afterlife.
You shall fear, Ismihan.
You shall fear.
Your eyes are the mirror of my eyes.
The fear you see in my eyes
is your own fear.
Not mine, Sheik Edebali.
The day you became with Osman
and betrayed Konya...
...your sheikdom ended.
So don't tire yourself up in vain.
Now...
I wish I could stay here and
talk to you more.
But...
...I have to welcome Osman.
Father, they'll hurt Osman!
Nothing happens unless Allah wills,
my daughter
He is the best of ambushers.
Their deception will be answered.
My sheikh, my father!
You're grieving too, I know that.
You say this to calm me down.
Aren't your tears for Osman Bey?
Look.
Ismihan united with infidels...
...and stives to harm her Muslim
sisters and brothers.
My tears are for the Islamic world
which is cut into pieces, my daughter.
Both Osman Bey's heart and strength...
...is able to overcome them.
But who will unite these Muslims like
Ismihan, who are blinded by their greed?
I think of this.
I cry for this, my daughter.
Humans break each other's hearts
for a temporary throne in this world.
The eyes of Muslims are
covered with dust and smoke.
How can you be a Muslim
by breaking others' hearts?
What Islam is this?
They spill their brothers' and sisters'
blood without a blink!
I weep for the despicable hearts
of those people, my daughter.
Which throne can defeat the
gratification of Allah?
I weep for the inattentive Muslims
who don't understand this, my daughter.
I cry for the Muslims who cannot
succeed in being a nation.
And they crush each other's heads
for a handful of wheat, my daughter.
How are we going to manage, my sheikh?
How are we going to overcome, father?
How will these Muslims gather themselves?
Look.
Let me tell you a story now, daughter.
Tariq bin Ziyad,
the conqueror of Al-Andalus.
The Blessed Commander.
He did not run away from the war
in the name of Allah.
And he always triumphed
with the allowence of Allah.
He did.
His commander,
who raised him to the rank of commander...
...instead of rejoicing for
the spread of the call of Islam...
...says Tariq bin Ziyad to stop.
"Stop already!"
There was no reason for him to stop.
In order to spread the word of Allah
all over the world...
...he disobeyed his commander
and moved on...
He said "Allah's call is
greater than my commander!"
But the commander of Tariq bin Ziyad...
...fumed because he didn't listen to him
Do you see it?
Both are heading towards the same goalç
But the commander of Tariq bin Ziyad...
...was defeated by his greed...
...he envied Tariq Bin Ziyad's victories.
There it is, my daughter.
What tore the nation apart is this envy.
However, we should remember Allah's command
He said, “Fight the infidels until there is
no sedition, and the only religion is Allah's."
“If they desist, don't push.
Enmity is only for cruels”
[Surah Al-Baqarah 193]
We will unite first and fight the infidels.
We will hold fast to the rope of Allah.
Then, even if all the world's evil,
idolaters, and hypocrites unite...
They will not be able to divide our nation.
There is no defeat for the nation that
clings to the rope of Allah, my daughter.
Wherever we are...
...We will not abandon our
fellowship and we will be united.
We will keep our hearts strong
against the infidels.
Inshallah, my sheikh.
Inshallah.
Nearly there!
Alps!
Take these buckets.
I'm coming, my dear Bala, I'm coming!
Come on Osman, come on Osman!
Let's work hard, let's work hard!
Come on, Olof.
See why I called you.
Come.
Come, Osman Bey, let's see.
What's going on, my Bey?
No problem, no problem.
Would you excuse me, my Bey?
Come
O Allah!
Oh Allah, in the name of Allah!
Take it.
What is that?
The mouse is advancing towards the trap.
I'm going to crush that mouse's head.
Other mice will take a lesson from it.
We will come out,
if Allah permits, my Bey.
We'll come out.
Hold on, my dear Bala.
Let's go
Stop, stop, stop.
The tunnel has appeared.
Give me that torch, I see it.
Let's look.
That's the place Samil mentioned.
Come on.
Easy.
Come on, come on, brother.
Come, Cerkutay, here.
Come.
Let's see
Come on.
- My Bey.
- Here.
Come on, come on.
Let's go.
- Boran!
- My Bey!
Boran, take the weapons.
Take the weapons.
Come on, come on.
So Osman is coming here.
I am grateful to you
for giving me this chance.
Osman doesn't expect
to see Olof in front of him.
Olof, you handed the castles
over to them with your own hands.
Now is the time to fix it.
For this reason...
...this is your revenge.
We'll make him pay for
everything he's done so far.
Come on, show your skills.
Osman will regret coming here.
We are starting.
Felic.
You are going somewhere else.
This path is dead.
My Bey, the passage must be
behind the wall.
Eyvallah, we will see.
Give me, give me this.
O Allah!
Samil, like you said,
this place hits the corridor.
We are on the right track.
Come on, keep going, keep going.
Come on, work hard, come on, work hard!
Harder!
Come on, my brothers.
Let's go.
My Bey!
Everyone take up their weapons!
Let's go Gurbuz.
Come on brothers!
Alps, we'll take my sheikh and Bala
without making any noise.
And after opening the doors...
...We will cut off the head of anyone
involved in this betrayal!
As you order my Bey!
Let's go.
Osman Bey is coming.
I told you not to backdoor him!
He is coming to a trap!
Ismihan Sultan, the mother Sultan,
she is a snake, Oktem.
Osman will not be able to
survive this time.
Hatun, we are talking about Osman Bey,
sheik Edebali, Bala Hatun!
We have to do something!
There is nothing we can do anymore!
The only thing we're going to do now is
to protect our heads.
We cannot contradict Mother Sultan,
she is not like Osman.
Mother Sultan is a demon, Oktem.
The castle will be a grave f
or them all, Bengi, a grave!
This is cruelty!
Oktem Bey, Oktem Bey!
Oktem stop!
If you are not thinking of yourself,
think of your daughter.
In the tiniest mistake we make,
we'll pay it with Alcicek's life.
I am also upset for them.
But there is nothing we can do.
Hatun, get away.
Oktem Bey, Oktem Bey!
It's your daughter!
It's Alcicek!
Don't you hear me?
The voices
come from this direction
They are coming, my Bey!
Cerkutay, hold there.
Don't worry my Bey.
We will show them.
Let's go
Boran.
- Come on, brothers!
- Come to me!
Come on brothers!
Bala.
Osman.
My Bala.
- My Bala.
- My Osman.
Osman.
Welcome, Osman.
Ismihan.
You again!
Bala, Bala, if you touch Bala...
Osman.
My sheikh.
We were waiting for you.
The only thing you are waiting for
is your death.
We are superior now Osman.
The few have overcome the many before.
I will defeat you badly.
You can't even imagine it.
Osman!
Did you think there would be
no return for your actions?
Don't you dare!
Bring Mesut, take your Hatun.
Hands off of her!
Ismihan, I will kill you!
Don't you dare touch Bala!
Don't you dare to hurt her hair!
Don't you dare to hurt her!
This is my last warning to you!
If you don't bring Mesut...
...I will cut her neck.
We are ready to sacrifice our lives,
Osman Bey.
Your dreams that will come true
will make you real.
Go.
- I'm not going anywhere
- We have to go, come on my Bey!
Go, Osman Bey, for your sons.
I will not go anywhere
They are your honesty, go for God's sake, go
My Bey, they keep coming over us!
We have to go out, come on, my Bey!
- My Bala
- Go.
We have to get out, my Bey!
- Bala!
- Osman!
- Sheikh!
You have to go for
the future of our community.
- No!
- Go Osman.
I can't go, my sheikh.
Osman, you have to go.
Come on, come on!
- Come on, come on.
- I'll come, Bala!
I'll come back!
What do you keep looking at
like curious women, Hussein?
Osman Bey is about to be here.
Our life depends half on Mother Sultan...
And the other half on Osman.
And you hang around here like this!
Stand tall!
And don't make me angry!
I am fully prepared, my Bey!
I am looking to see if there is a passage
connecting here to another place.
Infidels build
such corridors in their castles.
Oh Huseyin!
You birdrain Huseyin.
He assumes there's a secret tunnel,
and he assumes it's in our room.
Mother Sultan on one hand,
Osman on the other...
Also Huseyin.
Oh poor Bayindir.
You are always in trouble!
Come on, I won't stay here any longer.
Where to, Bayindir Bey?
To hell.
You want to come?
Bayindir, I really wonder.
To whom you are more loyal?
To your treasure, or mother Sultan?
What are you trying to say?
Get away.
Do not you dare.
The gold you stole from Olof and took
via the pact, the treasury.
Do you think that our Mother Sultan
does not know this richness of yours?
That you can sell everyone
at any moment for gold?
My treasury is my right.
Mother Sultan is another thing.
My treasure is a whole other thing.
No, not another thing.
Our Mother Sultan says
you will only choose one.
Otherwise, she will always
doubt your loyalty.
You know that the Mother Sultan
does not like suspicion
And those who makes her suspicous
are doomed to die.
What do you want? Tell me.
Not me, our Mother Sultan
demands that you prove your loyalty.
Good, I will stand against Osman.
I will help you trap him.
What does she want more of me?
Your gold that is
more precious than your soul!
You will give it all to
Mother Sultan's service.
Okay then.
I shall sacrifice them for our
Mother Sultan.
Both our lives and our wealth.
My Sultan, you came here
from Konya on horseback.
The carriage goes empty at the back.
Neither the horse is difficult for the Turk
nor the Turk is a burden on the horse.
The people will see me on the horse.
Mother Sultan's power may be insufficient
for those rebels.
They will see me as a leader with my army.
- Peace be upon you
- Peace be upon you too.
Welcome to the frontier lands,
Hadrat Sultan Aladdin.
Say your name.
You must have heard.
I am your servant, Turgut Bey.
I am here to serve you and
Mother Sultan.
Mother Sultan ordered me to welcome you
properly, and accompany you to Sogut.
Mother Sultan is in Marmaracik.
Why did she ask you to accompany
me to Sogut?
- Hadrat Sultan.
- Soldier!
Hadrat Sultan.
Do you think we weren't informed of the
theft of Mother Sultan's seal?
Do not blame me, Hadrat Vizier.
But the information you were given
is incomplete.
Mother Sultan got her seal back
before she killed Osman.
And I know that she holds very
important prisoners.
How will we know that
your tongue speaks the truth?
There is an endless army
behind you, Vizier.
We are not that crazy to deceive you.
What I would like to say, my Sultan...
It is for your best to go to Sogut
before Marmaracik.
Mother Sultan says that this
is the most important of all.
If you don't want to waste your life,
get out of our way
We will go to Marmaracik.
We are going to Sogut.
But, my Sultan....
Father.
How did you face all those
ignoble dogs?
How did you overcome
all this sedition?
You entrusted everything to me.
You thought I was fit for this.
You wanted to improve our inheritence.
You wanted to expand the Kayi.
Let's not leave our father alone, brother.
He said, "No one should come with me"
brother.
I do not hesitate to disobey our father
for the sake of him, brother.
I listened to my mother's words,
I left her alone.
At least we can stay
with our father, brother.
You say the right thing, my brother.
He does not need loneliness now,
he needs his children.
Father, you didn't have all these tribes
and Beys behind you.
And you didn't have all these alps
and you didn't have all that authority.
Tell me.
In such a dead end...
...what would you do?
What?
But...
Do not tell me as my father.
Noy as my Bey.
Tell me as Ertugrul Ghazi.
I know, of course, that my path
is certainly more difficult than before.
I know that my enemies are more
unjust than before.
You opened a path for us,
the path is bumpy and difficult.
But I will keep walking.
You are the one who made me
rule everyone.
No, I will not despair.
I will never despair, never.
I will back off
if necessary and give up if necessary
I even...
...I will sacrifice when the time comes.
I should not enter into a war in which
I will be defeated and destroyed.
It is time to accept the lost now.
Father.
As long as we have children these...
as long as you have grandchildren like these...
I should protect them.
Let them cut our branches.
Our roots are strong.
Sogut.
- Welcome Sultan Aladdin.
- You brought joy, my Sultan.
- Welcome our Sultan!
- Welcome!
- Welcome.
- Welcome
My Sultan! My Sultan!
My son is very sick. Please help.
My son is very sick.
- Welcome!
- Welcome, Sultan!
Welcome, my Sultan!
You have honored us, my Sultan.
Hadrat Sultan Aladdin.
The situation is bad, as you can see.
This is the situation that Osman Bey
put people into.
Mother Sultan wanted you to see
the situation beforehand.
We have seen it all now, Turgur Bey.
- Vizier.
- My Sultan.
Ask the healers of Konya so that this matter
can be resolved before the disease worsen.s
As ordered by Hadrat Sultan.
There is also a person in the inn
that Mother Sultan would like you to see.
Who is it?
Malhun Hatun.
Unlike Osman Bey, she worked hard to
fight against the disease in Sogut.
Let's see her.
We will quickly go to Marmaracik then.
I will stay here awaiting your order.
Either we will be dragged together.
Or we will give up the dream of
a state for the sake of those we love.
Or we will find a third way.
Like my father did.
Boran!
My Bey.
We are going to Sultan Mesut.
As you order, my Bey.
Marmaracik Castle.
Excuse me for
my audacity, Mother Sultan, but...
...sheikh Edebali, the light of Oghuz.
You won't hang him too, will you?
- If our community riots...
- If our people riot for a betrayer...
...they have to accept the
consequences, Bengi Hatun.
Both Sheikh Edebali and Bala's lives
are up to Osman.
If he surrenders and bows down...
...things may change.
I am amazed by your thoughts, Ismihan.
Oppressors like you are the ones
who caused the martyrdom of Hadrat Sumeyye.
But Allah Almighty punished
them for what they did
Their end is hell.
Look at that!
You are the one who decides who goes to
heaven and who goes to hell.
You are the symbol of arrogance.
I am not surprised.
Your end will be the same.
You will be deprived of the
mercy of Allah.
This will be enough for you.
The Sheikh's daughter must
not be so arrogant, sheikh Edebali.
If you had raised her properly at the time...
...Bala Hatun wouldn't be at the
door of death now.
And neither would you, of course.
My Allah, who did not leave Hadrat Yunus
alone in the belly of a whale...
...will certainly not leave us alone
in the hands of an oppressor like you.
I totally believe in Him.
As for you...
Ismihan Hatun...
Fire will surround your mouth.
Even talking to you is useless.
Avci, tie their mouths.
or else I will take their lives
before Osman arrives!
Welcome, my Sultan..
I am Malhun Hatun, Umur Bey's daughter,
Osman Bey's Hatun.
Sogut belongs to us.
And you are our guests
like Mother Sultan.
My mother obviously didn't make
things clear enough for you.
Everything that belongs to you
is ours, Malhun Hatun.
So please, my Sultan.
Act like you are in your property.
What is this situation?
The situation is bad, my Sultan.
Mother Sultan left Sogut
due to the disease.
And we struggle a lot.
The spread of disease
will definitely be stopped.
The wounds will certainly be healed.
But what Osman did...
He'll pay with his head.
You know that, right?
If I supported what my Bey did...
...I would not mention my father's name
first while introducing myself, my Sultan.
Great.
I called healers from Konya.
They will get here as soon as
possible and help you.
- I have no other business here.
- My Sultan.
We made all these preparations for you.
If you don't join us, we'll grieve.
Okay then.
My Sultan.
Call the chief!
There must be a chief of Sultan.
We should do like this, Malhun Hatun:
An ingredient can be good on its own,
and poison when mixed with another ingredient.
If we put the ingredients that will
put Sultan to sleep in different meals...
Sultan will fall into a deep sleep.
No evidence of this will remain,
but the chief shouldn't taste them first.
No, the chief will taste everything.
However...
If we put antidote too...
...the Sultan will sleep,
but the chief will not.
Thus, no one will suspect.
In the name of Allah,
Most Gracious, Most Merciful
- I myself cooked all of these, my Sultan.
- Come on hurry up.
Good to go, my Sultan.
I respect your decision, Osman Bey.
Eyvallah, my Sultan.
I told you in the beginning.
This is a big risk
You should have left me to death.
Not just for you.
I thought it would be a good move
for us too.
But that Ismihan...
She tied our hands!
- Forgive us if we made any mistake.
- No, no Osman Bey.
I was basically a dead man.
I used to lead armies in wars and terrorize
the enemy in battlefields in the past
But they made me rot.
But you gave me a purpose.
And now I am walking
towards death for this goal.
You have my blessings.
I give you my blessings too...
I certainly do.
Let's go
It was my destiny to die at the hands
of a friend while I fight the enemy
Let's go, Osman Bey.
Let's go.
We shall go.
- Thanks
- Enjoy it.
Prepare my horses, soldiers
We will go to Marmaracik.
How about resting a bit more?
My mother is waiting for me.
I don't want her to wait any longer.
I have prepared your room, my Sultan.
You came from a long way.
Your mother would also
be sad if she saw you so tired.
No.
I have to go to Marmaracik.
The Sultan is clearly tired.
My Sultan.
Please let us take you to your room.
You should rest.
Have a good sleep, my Sultan.
Sheikh Edebali, the greatness.
It's not possible, Hatun,
it's not possible.
We are never going to get rid of
this disgrace. Never.
We can't disobey the order, Bey.
This is not something
you can just watch, Hatun. It's Edebali.
All Turkmens will rise up.
You think Osman will catch up and not
let him hang, is that so, Bey?
Osman Bey has no other choice
except for surrendering, Hatun.
Near Iznik.
Who is there?
Do you invite me to meet
and set a trap for me? What's it?
Kantakouzanos, not everyone can know
the secret, not everyone can see us!
Welcome, Kantakouzanos.
You could have asked me to come alone.
I could have done this.
- Go ahead, I'm listening
- Come.
Our lands covered
all of this map years ago.
The people of Konya and Osman
imprisoned us.
I'm past the age of
taking history lessons.
If you have something to say, speak up,
otherwise you're wasting my time...
We're getting started, Kantakouzanos.
Konya had weakened Osman and
now his neck is under my sword.
We will destroy not only Osman,
but also Konya.
- ısmihan is my ally.
- She is not anymore.
We have been in touch with
Ghazan, the Mongol Khan for a while now
He is also annoyed by the problems here.
We will unite and crush them!
Everyone in these lands
will be our slaves.
The secret that will give us this power
has risen again.
Go ahead, I'm listening.
Our real ally will tell you the rest.
I bear witness that there is no God but Allah, and I bear
witness that Muhammad is His servant and Messenger
My Bey, is this the only solution?
Are you saying that
this is too difficult for you?
- We should come too, my Bey!
- Yes my Bey!
No, just me and Sultan Mesut.
Some wars are fought alone.
Sir, this cause is all of our cause.
We are together even when we are alone!
Eyvallah.
Eyvallah, Alps.
Osman Bey is coming.
- Bala.
- Osman.
Bala.
My sheikh.
Mesut, the impostor sultan
of the Seljuk state!
And his partner, the traitor, Osman.
You two disobeyed Sultan Aladdin.
So you are also with us, Vizier.
- Does Mother Sultan know this?
- No.
Neither Mother Sultan nor Sultan Aladdin.
No one knows.
I only serve myself.
So you say that you are a man
who cannot be trusted.
On the contrary, I am the man you trust
the most as long as our goals are the same.
Let's cut it short.
Tell me, what's the secret?
A relic was stolen from
Constantinople years ago.
Do you remember?
Holy cross.
It is in Osman's hands.
It was said that it went to Jerusalem
with a priest.
War is like this,
whether it is in politics or in the arena.
You know what the winners want you to know.
This is what Osman wanted you to know.
Why do you say this now?
As the Cardinal said,
we will unite at the order of Ghazan Khan.
We will destroy the unity of
Turks and Muslims on this land.
They will become our slaves.
Holy Cross will ensure this.
I know, and that's why we're sharing
this information with you.
Look, Vizier.
I'll take that cross.
But I want you to know this.
You too, like the Turks,
are guests in this land.
You are unwanted guests.
That's why when the war ends.
The lion's share is Byzantine's.
- All the secret...
- Vizier!
I only say my word once.
If you want to deal with me,
you have to agree to my terms.
What's happening here?
My head!
Soldier, prepare my horse.
We will go to Marmarcik.
You wanted Sultan Mesut, here he is.
You asked for me, and here I am.
She threatened me with
Bala and my sheikh.
Here I am.
- Hang them!
- What?
My sheikh!
Visit our website for more: turkision.com